<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AgnihotraTimeTable</string>

    <string name="drawer_open" translatable="false">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close" translatable="false">Close</string>
    <string name="imgContentDesc" translatable="false">Image Description</string>

    <string-array name="suported_languages">
        <item>en</item>
        <item>hi</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="toolbar_title">Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="lblinfo">Shri Madhavji Potdar Saheb \n 1915&#8211;1974 \n Agnihotra widhi ke punarujeevankarta</string>
    <string name="lblclick">Touch anywhere to continue</string>
    <string name="lblMenu">Menu</string>

    <string name="lstAbout_agnihotra">About Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="lstProcedure">Procedure</string>
    <string name="lstMantras">Mantras</string>
    <string name="lstAbout_madhavashram">About Madhavashram</string>
    <string name="lstGallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="lstContact_us">Contact Us</string>

    <!-- Location input fragment -->
    <string name="txtSearchByPlace">Search by place</string>
    <string name="txtSearchByLocation">Search by location</string>
    <string name="enterplace">Please Enter City Name</string>
    <string name="txtLatitude">Please Enter Latitude</string>
    <string name="txtLongitude">Please Enter Longitude</string>
    <string name="btnSelect">Select Date</string>
    <string name="btnGetTime"> Get Time</string>
    <string name="btnCurrentYear"> Current year</string>
    <string name="lblcopyright">Copyright © Madhavashram, Bhopal</string>

    <string name="january">January</string>
    <string name="february">February</string>
    <string name="march">March</string>
    <string name="april">April</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="june">June</string>
    <string name="july">July</string>
    <string name="august">August</string>
    <string name="september">September</string>
    <string name="october">October</string>
    <string name="november">November</string>
    <string name="december">December</string>

    <string name="lblDay">Day</string>

    <!-- About Agnihotra -->
    <string name="lblAboutAgnihotra">Agnihotra is a Yagnya to be performed throughout your life, everyday regularly at sunrise and sunset. All other Yagnyas are time bound and are performed for achieving a certain purpose.  Not so with Agnihotra which is to be performed every morning and evening without a break all through your life. It becomes part of your life or rather life  becomes purposeful and meaningful because of it.</string>
    <string name="lblPollutionSubHeading">Pollution and Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="lblAboutPollution">Agnihotra is a very simple and easy method to conquer the evils of pollution. Agnihotra purifies the atmosphere. The purification of the atmosphere purifies the Prana, the life energy, and thus Prana purifies the mind. For a happy living, purified mind is a necessity. Anybody who has the will and desire to lead life successfully and in a disciplined way, can adopt this practice of Agnihotra immediately.</string>
    <string name="lblSahab">Mahanubhav Shri Madhavji Potdar Saheb</string>
    <string name="lblAboutSahab">‘Propagation of Agnihotra in each and every household is the true form of Satya Dharma’ said Mahanubhav Shri Madhavji Potdar in 1963. Shri Potdarsaheb was born on 1st October, 1915 in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh. Father Shri Govindrao and Mother Smt. Radhabai Potdar’s second progeny came to be distinguishedly known by the name of Madhavji. Endowed with remarkable genius and great intelligence this bright child had established his distinguished identity in childhood itself. His academic education was completed in 1937. In that year Madhavji passed his B.Com. examination in First Class securing First position in the merit list of Lucknow University. He was awarded a Gold medal for this feat. On job front he worked for various companies and finally came to Bhopal in 1948 to work as the General Manager of Straw Products Limited. He worked here on this position for six years. While working here he earned a distinguished recognition for himself by becoming the most loved manager of all the workers of the Mill. He was like God of them. They worshipped him. ‘Saheb’ had a compassion filled mind. More than caring for his own privileges he passionately strived for getting others their rightful dues. ‘Saheb’s’ lavish life-style, aristocratic way of living was of the quality about which a common man longingly dreams. He was an expert in management techniques and hence was a consultant to many companies. His administrative abilities and skills were lauded everywhere. In life Potdarsaheb had everything – money, name and success but still he was not a self-centered person. His attitude was always that of a very charitable person who was ever ready to help the needy. Humanity was the greatest religion for him. He never believed in so-called religious ceremonies and connected rituals and therefore always kept himself away from such things.  In the year 1954, at the age of 39 years, a very powerful change took place in the life of the most honest, truth-abiding and kind  hearted   Potdarsaheb.
It so happened that ‘Saheb’ left the lucrative job and decided to start his own business. Incidentally in mid-May, 1954 he happened to meet Shri Gajanan Maharaj Rajimwale of Akkalkot, which is in Solapur district of Maharashtra. This meeting happened to cause such a deep impact on ‘Saheb’s’ mind that he became Shreeji’s follower for life. After staying for a week in Akkalkot he returned to Bhopal and established his new business in the name and style of Potdar Agencies Private Limited. The business was growing profitably and also rising ‘Sahab’s’ faith, devotion and love for Shreeji. Consequently this resulted in Shreeji taking him as his disciple by initiating him in June, 1957. Here onwards began the period of observing rigorous spiritual disciplines and penances. ‘Saheb’ being in the habit of doing any work whole-heartedly, totally concentrating the mind on the accepted job at hand and, therefore, soon he became fully and sincerely engrossed in the adopted spiritual disciplines. Under the guidance of his Sadguru he wrote some books like ‘Akkalkot Swami Parichay’ in Hindi and Shreeji’s Sanskrit composition ‘Sapta-shloki’s’ Hindi translation with elucidation and also some others. As a consequence of doing the Hindi translation of ‘Sapta-shloki’ he could perceive the importance of Vedas and also felt a growing fascination for them. In reality, however, all throughout his life, at no time, forget about studying them, ‘Saheb’ had never even seen the books of Vedas. On the basis of his own experiences ‘Saheb’ wrote a book in English – ‘In Search of Hapiness’. After going through it Shree told him to get the book printed. Accordingly on his 44th birthday, on 1st October, 1959 ‘Saheb’ presented his printed book to Shreeji. Soon hereafter, following Shreeji’s command, on the Vijayadashmi day of 11th October, 1959, in Shree’s presence and while offering oblations of water on the sacred ‘Paduka’s’ of Shree, Saheb took the vow “I will do the resuscitating work of Vedas with single minded devotion". Fifteen years ago, on the same lunar day of Vijayadashmi a similar vow was taken by Shreeji but in Potdarsahaeb’s vow the words “do-work of” and “with single minded devotion” were the only additions. Potdarsaheb had to do the practical work in the field to implement Shree’s vow into practice. The next fifteen years of his life were spent in fulfilment of this vow while facing tremendous hardships, making sacrifices at various stages, enduring everything as part of the rigorous penance. This period of 15 years depicted ‘Saheb’s’ life as a true propagater of religion, its each and every atom showing only unflinching faith, single minded devotion. During this testing period the kind of life ‘Saheb’ lived and whatever he did to further the cause is singularly remarkable. No family man could have shown such courage. However, ‘Saheb’ had made up his mind for total sacrifice and proved the word ‘Sacrifice’ meaningful. After taking the vow, on Shree’s command, ‘Saheb’ had gone on an all India propagation tour. During the five tours in five months, from 4th November, 1959 to 23rd March, 1960, he had propagated every where the message of Satya Dharma through his book ‘In Search of Happiness’. Later, Shree said that through the medium of these tours an important work of giving the divine message to all the four directions has been accomplished by Potdarsaheb, other than Potdarsaheb nobody else could have fulfilled this task. Agnihotra had not come into prevalence as yet. Though ‘Saheb‘had written about it in his book ‘In Search of Happiness’ but he had not outlined the process of its practice. He had only highlighted its importance and giving its history had actually challenged the scientific fraternity to undertake research to know the effects of yagnyas. Meanwhile, circumstances forced him to close down his business in August, 1961. With business gone income from practical sources came to a naught and now started the days of penury and miserable conditions. As it happens in such conditions, name and honour in society were lost and so also all the relatives and relationships. Now, here was standing with his vow a solitary man empty handed but standing valiantly and fearlessly with the resolve to fulfill it, come what may. In such circumstances came Agnihotra into existence in the sphere of ‘Saheb’s’ work. Though facing various odds his mind used to be constantly busy in contemplation. He had to propagate the five pathways of Satya Dharma viz. Yagnya, Daan, Tapa, Karma and Swadhyaya. The question he faced was which one to preach first and which one in the last and who would be able to practice all the five?
In reply to all these questions came the answer – Agnihotra. He realised that Agnihotra was easy to explain, getting its practice started too was not difficult and through its positive support it was possible the observance of other paths of this Dharma would gradually come into practice. After meditating for months over the matter he had come to the decision of introducing Agnihotra. No sooner the decision was arrived there came to meet him Shri Hiralal Sharma of Bairagarh, Bhopal. On Sharmaji’s showing keen interest in ‘Saheb’s’ work through him he got started on 22nd  February ,1963, the first morning - evening Agnihotra of two oblations. Thus 22nd February 1963 became the historical day when the first Agnihotra in the world was started. After this Saheb wrote an article on Agnihotra in March, 1963. During the year 1963, on the request of an institution named ‘Seekers of Happiness’ in Pune, Saheb had periodically sent 13 articles on Satya Dharma. Amongst these the second article was on Agnihotra. In 1964 these articles were printed in the form of a book and this book was given the name of ‘Dharamapath’. Saheb firmly believed that for all the problems and difficulties in life there is only one remedy and that is Agnihotra and hence he had dedicated Agnihotra to the populace. The preceptor, the preacher of Agnihotra is Saheb and Saheb alone. In 1962, two  books  were written by him. These were ‘Math, Mandir, Masjid, Gurudwara’ in Hindi verse and The Last Step in English prose. By 1966 about 8-10 Agnihotra had already started in India. There were 2-3 regular Agnihotra practitioners in Pune, 2 in Mumbai and 3-4 in Bhopal. In the month of March, 1966 Saheb had to leave Bhopal. He came to Ujjain. His family was with him. In the six member family the youngest member was only 4 years old. Difficulties continued to haunt him here in Ujjain too and yet passing through all odds Sahab started propagation work from 15th Februar, 1968. Almighty’s work do not require superficial means. Sahab’s propagation work kept spreading on the strength of his unflinching faith and it continued growing with positive results. Staying for two years in Ujjain Sahab returned to headquarter in Bhopal and untiringly worked very hard for the next 4 years. Meanwhile in 1971 he established ‘Panchratna Goshala’, a cow-pen, to facilitate easy availability of cow-dung cakes and cow’s pure ghee necessary for performing Agnihotra. In 1972 the mission mouth-piece, monthly ‘Dharmasoorya’ magazine was started and in 1973 Sahab successfully organised a ‘Manav Dharma Sammelan’. In January 1974 arranging a meeting of all the Pracharaks (propagators) spread all over India. He gave useful and effective directions for future course of action. With astonishing speed and planning for doing all this he fade farewell to the world on 9th June, 1974. Out of 58 years of his life he lived 15 years soulfully for us all. Lived for the re-establishment of Satya Dharma, a life which was full of unimaginable hardships. The member of practising Agnihotra had reached upto 5000 and there were hundreds of volunteer pracharaks actively working in the field. Sahab had become fully assured that now this work can not be stopped even if attempted by anybody. A kindly Saheb was an easygoing, very simple person and hence he faced deceit many times in life. As a ‘Pracharak’, propagator of Satya Dharma he worked selflessly for the welfare of the people without ever longing for name or fame. Not only this, the knowledge he attained through his own hard labour, sacrifices and penances all of that he handed over, delegated to the populace. This is why it becomes our moral responsibility to always remember him and his sacrifices. All over the world wherever Agnihotra is practised at all such places Saheb and Shreeji should be remembered alongwith Agnihotra.This Master–Disciple pair has rejuvenated the Vedas. Today Agnihotra is practised by millions of people and tomorrow this figure is going to be in billions. We have to keep in our memory the sacrifices Saheb has made for our sake otherwise it would seem that we too have deceived him. We are the people and people’s intention itself is divine intention. With benevolent grace whatever Saheb has given to us we are and would always remain thankful to him for it. Sahab’s biography ‘Mahanubhav ka Adbhut  Darshan’ is written by Jayant Potdar, Sahab himself has written ‘Paramsadguru’, Nalini Madhavji has authored ‘Sahab’. These books aptly narrate Sahab’s struggles and shows how, inspite of facing various odds, he worked for the rejuvenation of Agnihotra. However, today even ten percent of the Agnihotris do not know that their ‘Deity’ is Paramsadguru Shreeji and their ‘Ideal’ is ‘ShriSahab’. In this world whosoever is practising Agnihotra at whatever place he or she is fundamentally the follower of Sahab only. Ungreatefulness is inhuman. Therefore we should be greatful to Sahab who made many sacrifices and gave us Agnihotra. We should always remember this. </string>

    <!-- Procedure -->
    <string name="lblRulesHeading">Rules for Performing Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="lblRules1">1.  Definite Timings</string>
    <string name="lblRules2">2.  Pot to be used of a specific size and shape.</string>
    <string name="lblRules3">3.  Cow-dung cake fire</string>
    <string name="lblRules4">4.  Offerings (Oblations)</string>
    <string name="lblRequisitesHeading">Requisites for Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="lblRequisites1">1.  A receptacle (pot) in correct step-pyramid shape in prescribed dimensions made of copper or clay. This copper or clay ‘kund’ (pot) is available at Madhavashram. It can  not be had in market shops.</string>
    <string name="lblRequisites2">2.  Daily sunrise - sunset time table for the whole year applicable to the place of performance. Such a time table applicable to the place can be obtained by a request email to Madhavashram.</string>
    <string name="lblRequisites3">3.  Two drops of pure cow-ghee and few grains of whole, unbroken rice are sufficient for one time performance. 250 grams of unbroken rice grains and fifty grams of cow-ghee would be sufficient for a month’s performance (daily at sunrise and sunset). It would be easy to make this little quantity of cow-ghee at home every month if cow-smilk is available. Only cow-ghee is to be used for oblations in Agnihotra, no other kind of ghee is allowed.</string>
    <string name="lblRequisites4">4.  Dried cow-dung cakes prepared hygienically. Two small, thin, cow-dung cakes are sufficient  for the one time Agnihotra.</string>
    <string name="lblRequisites5">5.  Camphor crystals (deshi kapoor) and a matchbox for lighting the cow-dung cakes to prepare the fire for offering oblations in the copper or clay ‘kund’.</string>
    <string name="lblHowToPerformHeading">How to Perform</string>
    <string name="lblPerform1">Suppose the date today is 1st of July. Look into the time table to find out exact time of sunset. The time table tells you that the sun would set at 6 minutes past 7. So about 10 minutes before the sun-set time you should properly arrange the dry cow-dung cake pieces inside the pot leaving a little empty space in the center to place the camphor bits.</string>
    <string name="lblPerform2">Light the camphor bits with a matchstick, cow&#8211;dung pieces would burn and in about 8&#8211;9 minutes the fire in the pot would be ready for offering oblations.</string>
    <string name="lblPerform3"> A minute before the exact time of sunset, pick up a few grains of rice, smear them with two drops of cow-ghee, place them on your palm, divide  them into two equal parts.</string>
    <string name="lblPerform4">As the clock shows 6 minutes past 7, pick up one part of ghee-smeared rice grains with the fingers of your other hand, and chant the following mantra in clear, loud voice :</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra1">“Agnaye Swaha”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform5">Just as “swaha” is being uttered, drop the rice offering into fire in the pot (kund) with a neat smooth motion of your fingers. The offering would instantly burn emitting flame/smoke. Follow it up immediately with the chanting of second part of the mantra :</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra2">“Agnaye Idam Na Mama”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform6">This would complete the first mantra and the oblation. Next pick up the rest of the rice-grains placed on your palm, hold them in the fingers of your other hand, and make the second offering into the fire by chanting in the above manner the following mantra :</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra3">“Prajapataye Swaha”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform7">After offering , you must loudly chant.</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra4">“Prajapataye Idam Na Mama”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform8">This would complete the proceedings, the two offerings take around two minutes. The rice-grain burns  with a clear flame or could emit some smoke. You have to sit straight backed while performing Agnihotra, and look into the oblation flame in the fire pot as you make the offerings and chant mantras. Get up after the oblations are consumed by the fire, or you can do meditation, yoga, prayer, or your daily rituals after Agnihotra.</string>
    <string name="lblPerform9">The Sun-rise Agnihotra is performed similarly  at the exact time of sun-rise everyday. There is a little change in the first mantra chanted; the sunrise offering is made to Surya (Sun), hence the mantra at sun-rise Agnihotra is</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra5">“Suryaya Swaha”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform10">(Release the first offering.)</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra6">“Suryaya Idam Na Mama”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform11">The second mantra remains the same.</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra7">“Prajapataye Swaha”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform12">(Release the second offering.)</string>
    <string name="lblPerformMantra8">“Prajapataye Idam Na Mama”</string>
    <string name="lblPerform13">Everybody present at Agnihotra must join in chanting the mantra. Bathing is not a necessary condition for one to perform Agnihotra. However , it is advisable to take bath before performing the sunrise Agnihotra. Sunset Agnihotra can be performed after washing of hands and feet. The stress is on ensuring bodily cleanliness while performing Agnihotra.</string>

    <!-- Mantras -->
    <string name="lblSunriseMantraHeading">Sunrise Mantra</string>
    <string name="lblSunsetMantraHeading">Sunset Mantra</string>
    <string name="lblSunsetMantraEnglish1">Agnaye Swaha</string>
    <string name="lblSunsetMantraEnglish2">Agnaye Idam Na Mama</string>
    <string name="lblSunriseMantraEnglish1">Suryaya Swaha</string>
    <string name="lblSunriseMantraEnglish2">Suryaya Idam Na Mama</string>
    <string name="lblMantraEnglish3">Prajapataye Swaha</string>
    <string name="lblMantraEnglish4">Prajapataye Idam Na Mama</string>
    <string name="lblSunsetMantraHindi1">vXu;s Lokgk vXu;s bna u eeA</string>
    <string name="lblSunriseMantraHindi1">lw;kZ; Lokgk lw;kZ; bna u eeA</string>
    <string name="lblMantraHindi2">iztkir;s Lokgk iztkir;s bna u eeAA</string>

    <!-- About Madhavashram -->
    <string name="lblAboutMadhavashram">This is the place from where had started this Era’s first Agnihotra in the world. According to Indian almanac it was ‘Mahashivratri’ day and the date was 22nd February, 1963. On this day, in the evening, under the guidance and direction of Shri Madhavji Potdar Saheb the Agnihotra that was started by the resident of Bairagarh Kalan village Shri Hiralalji Sharma with the utterance of the mantra ‘Agnaye Swaha’, has today spread globally. It has spread everywhere to such a large extent that irrespective of any consideration of nationality, caste, creed, religion, colour, age or sex it has become a part of the life of the people of almost all nations throughout the world. With its beneficial results their lives have become happy, healthy and contented.
Mahanubhav Shri Madhavji Potdar Saheb apparently came to reside in his place of work ‘Madhavashram’, Bairagarh (Bhopal) in the year 1973. However, his work had already started in Bairagarh ten years ago. After getting started the first Agnihotra ‘Shrisaheb’ began its propagation work in 1968 from Ujjain. On reaching the figure of first 100 practitioners of Agnihotra he named his unregistered institution as ‘Satya Dharma Prachar Prasar’ and the sentence proclaiming its objective was ‘to be spread in each and every house and preached to every householder’. Amongst these first 100 Agnihotris the practitioners were mainly from the four states of Madhya Pradesh, Uttar Pradesh, Rajasthan and Maharashtra. In one year’s time this figure reached to 1000 and by 1973 it had crossed the figure of 4000. Thus, giving it a solid base and shape ‘Saheb’ said adieu to this world on 9th June, 1974. In the centre of Madhavashram is a small but elegant cottage ‘Sudarshan’ where the present Chief of the Ashram, Smt. Nalini Madhavji meets all the visitors everyday. Shree Says –</string>
    <string name="lblShreeSays">“Here only those will come whose welfare  is going to become a reality".</string>

    <!-- Gallery -->
    <string name="txtAgnidhaam">Agnidhaam</string>
    <string name="txtSahabSamadhi">Yugpravartak Mahanubhav Shri Sahab\'s Samadhi</string>
    <string name="txtMatajiSamadhi">Mataji\'s Samadhi</string>
    <string name="txtParshuramTemple">Bhagwaan Parshuram\'s Temple</string>
    <string name="txtParshuramIdol">Bhagwaan Parshuram\'s Idol</string>
    <string name="txtYagyashaala">Yagyashaala</string>
    <string name="txtKundYagyashaala">Kund in Yagyashaala</string>
    <string name="txtSudarshan">Sudarshan</string>

    <!-- Contact Us -->
    <string name="lblAddressHeading">Address :</string>
    <string name="lblAddress1">Mahanubhav Shri Madhavji Sansthan (Nyas)</string>
    <string name="lblAddress2">Madhavashram</string>
    <string name="lblAddress3">Seahore Road,</string>
    <string name="lblAddress4">Bairagarh, Bhopal (M.P.)</string>

    <string name="lblWebsite">Websites :</string>
    <string name="lblSite1">www.agnihotraindia.in</string>
    <string name="lblSite2">www.madhavashramindia.in</string>

    <string name="lblContactPersonHeading">Contact Persons :</string>

    <string name="lblContactPerson1">Vijayaji Potdar</string>
    <string name="lblPhone1">+91&#8211;9827052445</string>

    <string name="lblContactPerson2">Dr. Vivek Potdar</string>
    <string name="lblPhone2">+91&#8211;8120036303</string>
    <string name="lblEmail2">madhavashram@agnihotraindia.in</string>

    <string name="lblContactPerson3">Mr. Prasad Kushwaha</string>
    <string name="lblPhone3">+91&#8211;9826079446</string>
    <string name="lblEmail3">prasad@agnihotraindia.in</string>

    <string name="lblContactPerson4">Mr. Swapnil Tolambiya</string>
    <string name="lblPhone4">+91&#8211;9881724541</string>
    <string name="lblEmail4">swapniltolambiya@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="lblContactPerson5">Mr. Kanishk Bansode</string>
    <string name="lblPhone5">+91&#8211;9890553680</string>
    <string name="lblEmail5">kanishk.bansode@yahoo.com</string>

    <string name="search_place_internet_error_message">Could not find location. Please check your internet settings.</string>
    <string name="search_place_general_error_message">Could not find location.</string>
    <string name="error_dialog_Ok_button">OK</string>
    <string name="city_location_error_message">Could not fetch latitude/longitude of selected location</string>

    <string name="menu_current_location">Current Location</string>
    <string name="menu_savepdf">Save PDF</string>

    <!-- Common -->
    <string name="lblAM">A.M.</string>
    <string name="lblPM">P.M.</string>
    <string name="lblSunrise">Sunrise</string>
    <string name="lblSunset">Sunset</string>
    <string name="btnOK">OK</string>
    <string name="city_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="agnihotra" translatable="false">Agnihotra</string>
    <string name="ad_mob_app_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1559061333211273~6471866247</string>
    <string name="ad_mob_add_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1559061333211273/8662915312</string>
    <string name="blank_string" translatable="false">-</string>

    <string-array name="menu_array">
        <item>@string/lstAbout_agnihotra</item>
        <item>@string/lstProcedure</item>
        <item>@string/lstMantras</item>
        <item>@string/lstAbout_madhavashram</item>
        <item>@string/lstGallery</item>
        <item>@string/lstContact_us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_months">
        <item>@string/january</item>
        <item>@string/february</item>
        <item>@string/march</item>
        <item>@string/april</item>
        <item>@string/may</item>
        <item>@string/june</item>
        <item>@string/july</item>
        <item>@string/august</item>
        <item>@string/september</item>
        <item>@string/october</item>
        <item>@string/november</item>
        <item>@string/december</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="imageName_array">
        <item>@string/txtAgnidhaam</item>
        <item>@string/txtSahabSamadhi</item>
        <item>@string/txtMatajiSamadhi</item>
        <item>@string/txtMatajiSamadhi</item>
        <item>@string/txtParshuramTemple</item>
        <item>@string/txtParshuramIdol</item>
        <item>@string/txtYagyashaala</item>
        <item>@string/txtKundYagyashaala</item>
        <item>@string/txtSudarshan</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
